So we cover hospitalization of 24 hours or more,
which we call inpatient.
Additionally,
expenses up to 90 days before hospitalization and up to 180 days after hospitalization are
covered.  After that
you must have seen modern treatments nowadays.
People get their knee replacement done through
robotic surgery.  So That Comes
Under Modern Replay Treatments.
We also cover all the modern treatments.
Nowadays, day care treatments
like cataract, hernia, pile stone do
not require you to be admitted for 24 hours.  You go to the hospital, get your
surgery done and come back home.  All these
come under day care treatments.
We also cover all this in our plan.  Right?
Nowadays you will also see that
people have started going into Ayush Homeopathic Unani Sudha also.
People have started going into Panchakarma also.
Right?  People undergo Panchakarma sort of treatments.
So there are hospitals
which are certified by the Ministry of
AYUSH.  So my customer goes to that hospital and gets
his treatment done related to this
homeopathic, Ayurvedic and
Unani principles.  So you cover that also and
give it to your customer.
Ma'am can I interrupt?  Can I
please?  Or please
ma'am, some clients say that their
diabetes has increased and
they are taking Ayush treatment for its treatment.  Is that
covered?
Look ma'am, that Ayush treatment should not be done from anywhere.
It depends and if the
diabetes has increased then there is no
hospitalization.  So this is
normal treatment.  That is a part of
the OPD cover.  So we will not cover OPD in this.
If you have taken OPD then
you will get the same expense as OPD.
Depending on your medical policy, your
hospitalization is covered for 24 hours or more.
Now we are come up with day
care treatment where we are covering surgery.
We are also covering two hours of hospitalization.  He is cashless.  But
if he is taking any medicines for diabetes
and all that then that thing will not be covered.
Right?
Now.  So loyalty bonus.  What is loyalty bonus is that
we give 20% bonus to our customers every year.
Even if the claim comes, even if the
claim does not come.  For example, there
is a policy of Rs 10 lakh.  Every year you will get a bonus of ₹2 lakh.
So in 5 years that policy of Rs 10 lakh will become worth
Rs lakh to you.  So that comes
under loyalty bonus.  So even if a claim comes, you will
get the bonus.  Even if there is no claim, you will
get the bonus.  Unlimited Reset Unlimited
Restore.  Who will explain this to me?  Anybody?
How does Unlimited Restore work?  Does anyone
know anyone here?
So in any year if your sum insured is
exhausted.  If your sum
insured gets exhausted in any year, we
refill it up to the sum insured.
For example, took a policy of ₹1 lakh.  Your
first claim came to ₹8 lakh.  You will settle
because you have a sum insured of ₹1 lakh.  Now
you are left with ₹ lakh.  In the same year, your
claim of ₹5 lakh came again.  What would you
do?  If we have only ₹ lakh, then
we will take ₹ lakh from the base and ₹ lakh
from the reset and will give the claim of ₹ 5 lakh
to our customer.  I do
n't have any waiting period for reset.  Any
waiting period clause will no longer be applicable.
And now they cover the same person and the same illness.